

ABOUT ME

Currently in my final year as a student at the University of Sydney studying a Bachelor of Project Management (majoring in Software Engineering). I believe my inter-personal skills, education, experience and work ethic give me an excellent chance of standing out amongst the competition.

CONTACT

Address

Brighton Le-Sands 2216 NSW

Phone

0405 695 536

Email

peter a lees@hotmail.com



linkedin.com/in/peter-lees-ba14b433

REFERENCE

Rob Little - General Manager Pacific Tissue/Wolf Washrooms

Adam Degnan – Chief Operations Officer Enware Australia

Contact details available upon request

EDUCATION

University of Technology Sydney

2010



Masters of Engineering Management

Graduate Certificate of Engineering

Management

Specifically designed to emphasise the interface between engineering, technology and management.

University of Sydney

Pending Completion – 2017



Bachelor of Project Management – (Software Engineering)

Fundamental project management skills, theories and methods including project finance, statistics, analytics, risk management, organisational behaviour and psychology.

Applied Training Solutions

Business Management Cert III

2008

This qualification reflects the role of individuals who apply a broad range of competencies in a varied work context using some discretion, judgement and relevant theoretical knowledge.

Gymea T.A.F.E

Mechanical Engineering Cert III

1995

This qualification covers the skills and knowledge required to work as an Engineering Tradesperson - Mechanical within metal, engineering, manufacturing and associated industries

Gymea Technical High

Higher School Certificate

1992

Electives: Computing Studies, Physics & Chemistry

CERTIFICATES

- St Johns First Aid Remote Area
- Statement of Attainment L.M.A (Leadership Management Australia)
- Benchmark Internal Auditing
- DBR Intermediate Microsoft Office

LICENSES

- Qualified Supervisor Limited Electrical -Department of Fair Trading
- Class C License RTA
- Light Fork Truck Workcover N.S.W
- OH&S Consultation Workcover N.S.W
- EWP Type SL Elevated Platform Operators
- General Boat license N.S.W Maritime Authority
- OH&S Construction (White card) Workcover NSW

INTERESTS

- Volunteer Firefighter Deputy Captain N.S.W Rural Fire Service - Since 1990
- Lap swimming
- Climbing
- Surfing
- ASX stock market game
- Snowboarding
- Coding/programming
- Bushwalking and hiking
- Cross country skiing/camping
- Motorsports

EXPERIENCE

Technical Consultant

2014 - Current

C.A.L. Industry Solutions

Specialist in delivering tailored Quality & Maintenance Systems within the manufacturing industry.

Technical Advisor

2012-2014

CITIC-HIC Heavy Industry Division

Manufacturer and supplier of processing equipment within the mining Industry. Successfully completed grinding mill installations in Zambia, Sierra Leone, Laos

and Philippines.

Process/Project Engineer

2011-2012

Omni Engineering/FP Group

Upgrade of clients site to meet Workcover OHS&E standards for plant equipment protection (Capital expenditure approximately 1.2 million). Fulfilled role as Process Engineer on main production line whilst implementing primary project.

Quality Assurance Manager

2007-2011

Enware Australia

Leading manufacturer of specialist safety systems and tapware. Implementation of multiple TQM initiatives resulting in reduced product and process costs whilst increasing the companies reputation for quality within the industry.

Maintenance Manager

2004-2007

Enware Australia

Manager of Maintenance and R&D workshops. Implementation of planned maintenance systems across multiple sites to increase production efficiency through reduced downtime. Design and manufacture of various prototypes in conjunction with R&D department.

Difficult Access Consultant

2002-2004

Anchor Point Access

Qualified T.R.A.C. (Technical Rope Access Concept) operator, Industrial rope access VM – Level 2

Maintenance Supervisor

Australian Plastic Profiles

2000-2004

Afternoon Shift supervisor responsible for repair of all mechanical and electrical breakdowns and general maintenance of plant equipment and site.

Maintenance Engineer

1993-1998

Hannan Print

Trade qualified Mechanical Engineer responsible for repair of all mechanical breakdowns, installation and general maintenance of plant equipment and site.